miclad.com 2014-02-27

# Home

**Privacy Policy**

Supertophost.com, LLC is committed to protecting client data collected. Supertophost.com respects client's privacy and use of Supertophost.com services indicates agreement to Supertophost.com privacy policy guidelines as defined: Supertophost.com will collect and record minimum required client information in order to provide competitive services. Supertophost.com privacy policy states the kinds of processes that may occur in different circumstances when client data will be collected. Usage of Supertophost.com grants the right to collect user information

Supertophost.com may record any or all information given by client according to transaction type client enters, such as date of birth, name, address, phone numbers, fax numbers, email addresses, website use, and other personal information needed to process request.

Supertophost.com will strictly use required information and data on client to process request or task made. Supertophost.com will enforce reasonable measures needed to prevent unauthorized access to such information. In certain cases, Supertophost.com may require additional forms of identity from client to safeguard such information.

Client internet browsers have in-built mechanisms to store small files or cookies that have information to help websites recognise client account. Supertophost.com may use such facility to increase user experience. However, user may choose to prevent user computer from accepting cookies, which may impair some of the website's functions.

Supertophost.com will not disclose any personal information received from client to third parties. Supertophost.com may use such information to notify or inform client about developments and other Supertophost.com services or offers. However, client or user will be given the option to remove self from such a mailing list or notification processes. Supertophost.com will not disclose information collected on website to third parties without consent and acknowledgement from client/user. Supertophost.com may provide general survey or data information to third parties but will withhold those that may identify individuals.

DISCLOSURE TO LAW ENFORCEMENT

Supertophost.com reserves the right to disclose subscriber information to law enforcement agencies without consent or notifying subscriber if lawful request is made from such agencies. Supertophost.com will cooperate fully with such law enforcement agencies.

POLICY CHANGES

Supertophost.com may change its Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. Reasonable steps will be made to inform clients/users. However, clients are encouraged to check for updates every time they enter the website to ensure it meets their approval. Changes will be made directly to Privacy policy and such future changes will supersede the prior version.

CONTACT US

Clients and users are encouraged to contact Supertophost.com directly if any questions should arise or they need clarification about information collected. Factual errors in such information or removal of details from list under Supertophost.com may also be made this way

**N.B:**  This policy covers how we use your personal information. We take your privacy seriously and will take all measures to protect your personal information.

Any personal information received will only be used to fill your order. We will not sell or redistribute your information to anyone.
